https://uneedhardware.com/policy/privacy.php

Custom & OEM Hardware
Polished Brass (605/US3)
Satin Brass (606/US4)
Antique Brass (609/US5)
Oil-Rubbed Bronze (613/10B)
Polished Chrome (625/026)
Satin/Brushed Chrome (626/26D)
Polished Nickel (618/014)
Satin/Brushed Nickel (619/015)
Antique Nickel/Pewter (620/15A)
Matte Black (622/019)
Stainless Steel (630/32D)
Brass/Chrome (605/625)
Bamboo (BAMBOO)
Chrome/Chrome Wire (CHROME)
Wood (WOOD)
White/White Wire (WHITE)
U Need Hardware - Privacy Policy
At UneedHardware.com, we understand your concern for privacy and ensure that all information you choose to share with us is handled in the most safe and responsible manner. We have undertaken to create a safe online environment and implemented high security standards to establish a comfortable and safe shopping environment you deserve.
UneedHardware.com continuously gathers online customer activity and information in order to make the necessary enhancements for improving the online shopping experience of our users. Your personal information such as name, address, telephone number, credit card number, and e-mail address, which then are collected allow us to achieve this objective.
Furthermore, as our official company policy, U Need Hardware Co. does not under any circumstance sell or discloses its customer information to any third party. We protect your information by storing it on a secure web server in a private database.
Periodically, we send email messages containing special sales and promotions to the members on our mailing list. However, if you wish to opt out or unsubscribe from receiving e-mail communication from Uneedhardware.com or wish to be taken off the mailing list, you may do so by contacting us through email at: privacy@uneedhardware.com.
Here are ways we gather information and how we use it:
Orders
While ordering our products we request the following personal information from you in our registration form: first and last name, billing/shipping address, telephone number, email address, username, password, password hint, credit card, and credit card number. This is the information we need to process your order. Your telephone number is required to complete the registration or order process, so that we can use it to contact you about your order if we need to. Your billing information is also used to ensure that the right person is charged for the merchandise ordered.
Secure Shopping
By using our website, you consent to the usage and collection of information from you by U Need Hardware Co. and Uneedhardware.com. Any revisions or changes made to our Privacy & Security Policy will be posted on our website for view in order for our users to be informed of what information we collect, how it is used and under what circumstance, if any, is disclosed.
Cookies & Submissions
Cookies are small bits of electronic information that a web site can transfer to your hard drive to keep records of your visit. The use of cookies is standard on the Internet and many of the websites. At Uneedhardware.com, we use cookies as a tool to personalize your online shopping experience and assess our efforts to provide an easier, more streamlined online shopping experience. For example, cookies can be utilized to recognize you as a repeat customer each time you visit our site; it allows us to retrieve your order history and personal information so you do not have to re-enter it every time you shop. This means you can store items in your shopping bag between visits and maintain your very own special events calendar and address book. Another cookie lets us know what pages you visit as well as your browsing, shopping, and searching patterns. This enables us to identify ways to customize our online shopping environment to the preferences of our customers.
You have the option to refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. However, if you disable the cookies, you may not be able to place or track an order (see the Help section of your browser for instructions on how to disable cookies). Should you choose to disable cookies and cannot place an order on our site; you can always place the order by phone or email.
We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Uneedhardware.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers, if any.
Disclosure to Authorities
UneedHardware.com fully cooperates with law enforcement agencies working to identify those who may use our services for illegal activity. Accordingly, we reserve the right to disclose any and all information to lawful government bodies or officials under certain circumstances as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with an investigation of fraud or other activity that is illegal or may expose us to legal liability.
Access to Personally Identifiable Information
If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by making the change on our member account information page or by emailing our Customer Support Dept. at: info@uneedhardware.com or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.
Your consent
UneedHardware.com wants to make sure that our customers will undergo the most secure and risk-free possible online shopping experience and we want you to have as much faith in the security of your transaction as you do with our products and services. To this end, we have implemented several programs to ensure that you feel comfortable and satisfied to purchase our products.
UneedHardware.com guarantees that any sensitive information provided by the customer is protected online; all of your transactions completed through Uneedhardware.com go through strict security methods to ensure that your personal information is protected. All your information (such as credit card number or address) is transmitted using secure socket layers technology (SSL) encryption at 128 bits (the current industry standard) to communicate securely without risk of manipulation, impersonation or tampering of sensitive personal information. We utilize this encryption during the online checkout process, including the acceptance of your credit card information, and the management of your account. Furthermore, as a company policy, we believe in guarding your personal information not only online but offline as well. As such, access to your personal information is limited only to the staff required to fulfill the duties related to your account, for instance, order fulfillment, billing and the servers, hard drive and file cabinets that store your sensitive and personal data are placed in a secured and safe setting away from possibility of incursion.
What's more, every transaction you make with us comes with a fraudulent charge protection. In general, under federal law, you will not be liable for more than $50 of fraudulent charges. In the unlikely event that you are charged, we will reimburse you up to $50, provided these fraudulent charges were made without your knowledge and consent as a result of shopping at Uneedhardware.com.
All in all, we trust you will undergo a safe and secure shopping experience with us as we have taken significant measures in protecting your identity and security.
Changes in this Privacy Statement
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our website.
Should you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, Please contact us:
Phone: 800-292-6309
Email: info@uneedhardware.com
Postal Mail: PO BOX 1898, Walnut, CA 91788
HOME
ABOUT US
OUR PRODUCTS
FAQ
OUR POLICIES
SITEMAP
Shop with confidence at UneedHardware.com with our commitment to great quality products, prompt delivery, and a dedicated customer care team with knowledgeable product specialists. U Need Hardware offers specialty builders hardware, residential and commercial door hardware including solid brass door bolts, flush bolts, surface bolts, door stops, floor stops, pocket door pulls, bath accessories, cabinet knobs and pulls, and affordable storage organization solutions with bath vanity organizers, kitchen cabinet organizers, including a variety of drawer base organizers, pantry pullouts, lazy susans, and blind corner organizers. We take great pride in showcasing our products and strive to make your shopping experience the best at UneedHardware.com.
Copyright © 2020 U Need Hardware. All rights reserved.
Powered by ecMidas
